Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Princess Royal, this is the place.
الأميرة الملكية، هذا هو المكان.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
This is the best I could find
هذا هو أفضل ما يمكنني العثور عليه
for you here, Princess Royal.
لك هنا، الأميرة الملكية.
Please bear with it for now.
من فضلك تحمل الأمر في الوقت الراهن.
We've traveled all day.
لقد سافرنا طوال اليوم.
Come rest, Princess Royal.
إرتاحي يا أميرة الملكية.
Princess Royal, have some water first.
أيتها الأميرة الملكية، تناولي بعض الماء أولاً.
What did you give me to drink?
ماذا أعطيتني للشرب؟
It's so bitter.
إنه أمر مرير للغاية.
Forgive me, Princess Royal.
سامحيني يا أميرة رويال.
It's well water.
إنها مياه البئر.
The commoners drink this to quench thirst.
يشربه عامة الناس لإرواء العطش.
You...
أنت...
haven't left the palace with me enough.
لم يغادروا القصر معي بما فيه الكفاية.
You're not as steady as Rong Heng.
أنت لست ثابتًا مثل رونغ هينج.
Rong Heng...
رونغ هنغ ...
What happened to him?
ماذا حدث له؟
Why won't you let me out?
لماذا لا تسمح لي بالخروج؟
We're just following orders.
نحن فقط نتبع الأوامر.
Please stay calm inside, Princess Royal.
من فضلك حافظي على هدوئك في الداخل، يا أميرة رويال.
Eunuch A Fu.
خصي أ فو.
Brings the City Lord's decree.
يُحضر مرسوم سيد المدينة.
Princess Royal Su Feng'er has acted improperly.
لقد تصرفت الأميرة الملكية سو فينغ'ر بشكل غير لائق.
She intended to rebel.
لقد كانت تنوي التمرد.
She is demoted to commoner.
تم تخفيض رتبتها إلى عامة الناس.
Never allowed to enter the palace again.
لم يسمح لي بالدخول إلى القصر مرة أخرى.
Eunuch A Fu...
خصي فو...
What does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
I didn't do it.
لم افعل ذلك.
I want to see the Empress Mother.
أريد أن أرى الإمبراطورة الأم.
Rong Heng tried to assassinate the City Lord last night.
حاول رونغ هينغ اغتيال سيد المدينة الليلة الماضية.
He confessed and was punished.
اعترف وتمت معاقبته.
In your palace, Rong Heng
في قصرك، رونغ هينغ
was found with letters colluding with officials.
تم العثور على رسائل تحتوي على تواطؤ مع مسؤولين.
Letters plotting rebellion.
رسائل التخطيط للتمرد.
The City Lord issued this decree.
أصدر سيد المدينة هذا المرسوم.
Look at these yourself.
أنظر إلى هذه بنفسك.
It is my handwriting.
إنها خط يدي.
But I didn't write these.
ولكنني لم أكتب هذه.
Eunuch A Fu...
خصي فو...
Do you believe me?
هل تصدقني؟
I want to see the Empress Mother.
أريد أن أرى الإمبراطورة الأم.
The City Lord just coughed up blood in anger.
لقد سعل سيد المدينة للتو الدم من شدة الغضب.
He has already issued the decree.
وقد أصدر المرسوم بالفعل.
No one is allowed to see him.
لا يسمح لأحد برؤيته.
Coughing blood?
سعال الدم؟
Why would the Empress Mother cough blood?
لماذا تسعل الامبراطورة الدم؟
Eunuch A Fu...
خصي فو...
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Guard Yang.
الحارس يانغ.
You've suffered, Princess Royal.
لقد عانيت، يا أميرتي الملكية.
How is Rong Heng now?
كيف حال رونغ هينغ الآن؟
Why did she try to kill the Empress Mother?
لماذا حاولت قتل الامبراطورة الام؟
I've been investigating secretly.
لقد كنت أقوم بالتحقيق سراً.
I only know she's being held in secret.
كل ما أعرفه هو أنها محتجزة سراً.
As for where she's held,
أما بالنسبة لمكان احتجازها،
I have no way of knowing.
ليس لدي وسيلة لمعرفة ذلك.
I see...
أرى...
Can you arrange for palace guards
هل يمكنك ترتيب حراس القصر؟
to let me in to see the Empress Mother?
هل تسمحون لي برؤية الإمبراطورة الأم؟
This matter...
هذا الأمر...
I'm truly powerless to help.
أنا عاجز حقا عن المساعدة.
I was once commander of the armies,
لقد كنت قائدا للجيوش ذات يوم،
but now my influence is gone.
ولكن الآن اختفى تأثيري.
It's hard for you too.
إنه أمر صعب بالنسبة لك أيضاً.
I have one more favor to ask.
عندي طلب آخر أريد أن أطلبه.
Find out exactly where Rong Heng is held.
اكتشف بالضبط أين يقع Rong Heng.
It will help us uncover the truth.
وسوف يساعدنا على اكتشاف الحقيقة.
Your matters are my family's matters.
أمورك هي أمور عائلتي.
Besides, General Rong has helped me.
وبالإضافة إلى ذلك، فقد ساعدني الجنرال رونغ.
I will do all I can.
سأفعل كل ما بوسعي.
To fulfill your request.
لتلبية طلبك.
I'll wait here for your news.
سأنتظر أخبارك هنا.
Yes.
نعم.
Young Master.
السيد الشاب.
You've been silent since leaving the palace.
لقد كنت صامتًا منذ مغادرة القصر.
We could've returned to Yue.
كان بإمكاننا العودة إلى يوي.
Why stay here?
لماذا البقاء هنا؟
To be a teacher?
أن تكون معلما؟
Young Master...
السيد الشاب...
Ruolin...
روولين...
What do you think of Princess Royal?
ماذا تعتقد عن الأميرة الملكية؟
Princess Royal was terrible to us.
الأميرة الملكية كانت فظيعة معنا.
Now she's banished from the palace.
والآن تم نفيها من القصر.
She brought it on herself.
لقد جلبت ذلك على نفسها.
Can you say exactly
هل يمكنك أن تقول بالضبط؟
how she was terrible to us?
كم كانت فظيعة معنا؟
Can't remember, can you?
لا أستطيع التذكر، أليس كذلك؟
This time,
هذه المرة،
because of leaving the palace,
بسبب مغادرة القصر،
I couldn't tell right from wrong.
لم أستطع التمييز بين الصواب والخطأ.
I became someone else's pawn.
لقد أصبحت بيدقًا لشخص آخر.
And I harmed Princess Royal.
و أذيت الأميرة الملكية.
We must help her fix this.
يجب علينا مساعدتها في إصلاح هذا الأمر.
We can't leave yet.
لا يمكننا المغادرة بعد.
Will you help me?
هل ستساعدني؟
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Sit.
يجلس.
Shopkeeper, what are you staring at?
يا صاحب المتجر، ما الذي تحدق فيه؟
Clear the place.
نظف المكان.
Why clear the place?
لماذا تطهير المكان؟
Shopkeeper.
صاحب متجر.
Don't you recognize our Princess Royal?
هل لا تتعرف على أميرتنا الملكية؟
Princess Royal or not,
أميرة ملكية أم لا،
here in my place,
هنا في مكاني،
everyone's just a guest.
الجميع مجرد ضيوف.
If you have money, you eat here.
إذا كان لديك المال، يمكنك تناول الطعام هنا.
No money, go somewhere else.
لا يوجد مال، اذهب إلى مكان آخر.
You...
أنت...
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
I am magnanimous.
أنا كريم.
I won't argue with her.
لن أتجادل معها.
Xiao Tao.
شياو تاو.
Shopkeeper.
صاحب متجر.
What food do you have today?
ما هو الطعام الذي تناولته اليوم؟
Serve it all to our Princess Royal.
قدم كل هذا إلى أميرتنا الملكية.
We have food,
لدينا طعام
but some can't afford it.
لكن البعض لا يستطيعون تحمل تكاليف ذلك.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
I am Princess Royal of Jincheng.
أنا الأميرة الملكية جينتشنغ.
I didn't want to argue with you.
لم أكن أريد الجدال معك.
But you keep pressing me.
ولكنك تستمر بالضغط علي.
Princess Royal...
الأميرة الملكية...
You're just a commoner now.
أنت مجرد شخص عادي الآن.
Stop pretending to be Princess Royal.
توقف عن التظاهر بأنك أميرة ملكية.
Eat or don't, I don't care.
أكل أو لا تأكل، لا يهمني.
Xiao Tao.
شياو تاو.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Old lady,
السيدة العجوز،
Are you all right?
هل انت بخير؟
Get up quickly.
انهض بسرعة.
Let go.
اتركه.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Mother.
الأم.
Where did you bump yourself?
أين صدمت نفسك؟
Do you not watch where you're going?
ألا تلاحظ أين تذهب؟
Sir, you misunderstood.
سيدي، لقد أخطأت الفهم.
We didn't bump into her.
لم نصطدم بها.
I just helped her up.
لقد ساعدتها للتو على النهوض.
Right, you didn't bump her.
حسنًا، لم تصطدم بها.
Could my mother fall on her own?
هل من الممكن أن تسقط أمي بمفردها؟
Look.
ينظر.
And you say it wasn't you.
وأنت تقول أنه لم تكن أنت.
It's all right, Mother.
لا بأس يا أمي.
Fine.
بخير.
Today was my fault.
اليوم كان خطئي.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Stop.
قف.
Forgive?
سامح؟
My mother is past her prime years.
لقد تجاوزت والدتي سنوات ذروتها.
If anything happens because of this,
إذا حدث أي شيء بسبب هذا،
can you bear the consequences?
هل تستطيع تحمل العواقب؟
What's so hard to bear?
ما هو الشيء الصعب جدا تحمله؟
Isn't it just paying money?
أليس الأمر مجرد دفع المال؟
Money, right? Hand it over.
المال، صحيح؟ سلمه.
Thirty taels of silver.
ثلاثون تايل من الفضة.
Hand it over. What?
سلمها. ماذا؟
Thirty taels.
ثلاثون تايل.
Give it here.
أعطيها هنا.
Xiao Tao.
شياو تاو.
Give the money.
أعط المال.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Princess Royal only has twenty taels left.
الأميرة الملكية لم يتبق لديها سوى عشرين تايل.
Hand it over.
سلمها.
Twenty taels of silver.
عشرون تايل من الفضة.
Princess Royal, huh?
الأميرة الملكية، هاه؟
You're getting off easy today.
لقد حصلت على النجاة بسهولة اليوم.
It's all right, Mother.
لا بأس يا أمي.
I'll take you to see a doctor soon.
سأأخذك لرؤية الطبيب قريبًا.
Xiao Tao, let's go.
شياو تاو، دعنا نذهب.
Princess Royal, it's time to eat.
الأميرة الملكية، حان وقت الأكل.
Xiao Tao.
شياو تاو.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
have I never considered others?
هل لم أفكر في الآخرين أبدًا؟
Never thought for anyone else?
لم أفكر في أي شخص آخر؟
Why do you say that, Princess Royal?
لماذا تقولين ذلك يا أميرة رويال؟
After what happened today,
بعد ما حدث اليوم،
I've been thinking,
لقد كنت أفكر،
back in the palace,
العودة إلى القصر،
I always did whatever I wanted.
لقد فعلت دائمًا كل ما أريد.
Just followed my own will.
لقد اتبعت إرادتي فقط.
Don't think that way, Princess Royal.
لا تفكري بهذه الطريقة، يا أميرتي الملكية.
Princess Royal is of noble birth.
الأميرة الملكية من أصل نبيل.
People like us,
الناس مثلنا،
were born to serve you.
ولدنا لخدمتك.
Are people truly born noble or lowly?
هل يولد الإنسان نبيلًا أم متواضعًا حقًا؟
What Princess Royal says,
ماذا تقول الأميرة الملكية،
I really don't understand.
انا حقا لا أفهم.
All I know
كل ما أعرفه
is to serve my mistress well.
هو أن أخدم سيدتي جيدا.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Let's eat first.
دعونا نأكل أولا.
Xiao Tao.
شياو تاو.
Sit down and eat with me.
اجلس وتناول الطعام معي.
No.
لا.
Servants don't eat with their mistress.
الخدم لا يأكلون مع سيدتهم
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
we'll rely on each other here.
سوف نعتمد على بعضنا البعض هنا.
Starting now,
ابتداء من الآن،
we'll call each other sisters.
سوف نسمي بعضنا البعض الأخوات.
Let's eat.
دعونا نأكل.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
I'm full.
أنا ممتلئة.
I'll go gather the clothes.
سأذهب لجمع الملابس.
You finished so quickly?
انتهيت بهذه السرعة؟
Xiao—
شياو؟؟؟
Boss.
رئيس.
Can you tell me how much this is worth?
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني كم يساوي هذا؟
This isn't worth much.
هذا لا يستحق الكثير.
Not worth much?
لا يستحق الكثير؟
If it was from the palace, it'd be valuable.
لو كان من القصر، سيكون ذو قيمة.
It is from the palace.
إنه من القصر.
How can you prove it's from the palace?
كيف يمكنك إثبات أنها من القصر؟
Besides,
بجانب،
how would palace things end up with you?
كيف ستنتهي الأمور في القصر معك؟
Don't worry about that.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
Just tell me its price.
فقط أخبرني بالسعر.
Five taels of silver.
خمسة تايل من الفضة.
So little, even if it's from the palace?
قليل جدًا حتى لو كان من القصر؟
It's valuable but rare to sell.
إنها ثمينة ولكن من النادر بيعها.
If you won't pawn it,
إذا كنت لن ترهنه،
go try somewhere else.
اذهب وحاول في مكان آخر.
If you come back, the price drops.
إذا عدت، سينخفض ​​السعر.
Pawn it.
رهنها.
Xiao Tao.
شياو تاو.
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
You're finally back.
لقد عدت أخيرا.
Where did you go?
أين ذهبت؟
You worried me so much.
لقد أقلقتني كثيرًا.
Guess what I brought you.
خمّن ماذا أحضرت لك.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
Smells so good! Take a look.
رائحته طيبة جدًا! ألقِ نظرة.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Princess Royal.
الأميرة الملكية.
Where did you get all this money?
من أين حصلت على كل هذه الأموال؟
I found some work today.
لقد وجدت بعض العمل اليوم.
Try it quickly.
جربها بسرعة.
You eat. You go first.
أنت تأكل، أنت تذهب أولاً.
I still have more.
لا زال لدي المزيد.
Go on, eat. Don't be shy.
إذهب، كُل. لا تكن خجولاً.
Then let's eat together.
إذن فلنأكل معًا.
It smells so good.
رائحتها طيبة جداً.
It's been so long since we had
لقد مر وقت طويل منذ أن كان لدينا
meat this delicious.
اللحوم لذيذة للغاية.
Eat more.
تناول المزيد.
This palace treasure—
هذا كنز القصر؟؟؟
None of you have seen it, right?
لا أحد منكم رأى ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Don't touch.
لا تلمس.
If you break it, you can't pay for it.
إذا كسرته، فلن تتمكن من دفع ثمنه.
Mr. Xie.
السيد شيه.
You're very knowledgeable.
أنت على دراية كبيرة.
Please enlighten us.
أرجو أن تنيرنا.
All right.
حسنًا.
Where did you get this item?
من أين حصلت على هذا العنصر؟
A noble pawned it here a few days ago.
لقد رهنها أحد النبلاء هنا منذ بضعة أيام.
Where is this person?
أين هذا الشخص؟
At—
في؟؟؟
At the bun shop on the east side of the street.
في محل الكعك على الجانب الشرقي من الشارع.